[Opening backing vocal sound]
backing-event-01
[Opening hook backing]
backing-event-02
[La/na backing vocalization]
backing-event-03
[Undone backing repeats]
backing-008
What kind of monster would you like to make now?
backing-009
That last one set the town on fire.
backing-010
Now make one that is twice as mean.
backing-event-04
[Chorus backing / sustained hook]
backing-hook-1
Loose, oh my.
backing-event-05
[Hook tail]
backing-020
Choose your favorite monster beast.
backing-021
Suit the way you wanna be, be, be.
backing-022
Hunting Ed, head hunting Ted.
backing-023
Hide and seek's the game that monsters play.
backing-event-06
[And play backing / tail]
backing-025
And play.
backing-event-07
[Repeated backing / tail]
backing-vocalization-2
[Backing hook / vocalization]
backing-event-08
[Backing tail]
backing-event-09
[Short backing sound]
backing-event-10
[No way / yes way backing or vocalization]
backing-049
Choose your favorite monster beast.
backing-050
Suit the way you wanna be, be, be.
backing-051
Hunting Ed, head hunting Ted.
backing-052
Hide and seek's the game that monsters play.
backing-053
And play, and play, and play, and play.
backing-vocalization-3
[Closing backing sound / tail]